Let us now look at another
现在让我们来学习轮播
interesting JavaScript component in Bootstrap called the carousel.
另一个 Bootstrap 的有趣的 JavaScript 组件
The carousel allows you to present a slideshow on your webpage.
轮播允许你在你的网页中像幻灯片一样 展示一系列内容
Let's take a look at an example and
接下来让我们先看一个栗子
then we'll come back and consider the carousel in more detail.
然后再讨论其细节
Going to our webpage,
进入我们的网页
you can see that I have already included the carousel component on the webpage.
你可以看到我已经在这里引入轮播了
So you can see that the carousel presents a set of slides that will keep
接着 你可以看到这个轮播在不断地 展示一些内容
sliding from left to right on the webpage.
而且还有一个挺漂亮的向左滑的过渡动画
So this is an interesting way of presenting content to the users.
我想你会赞成这是一个很有趣的展示内容的方法
So a carousel is an interesting component that allows us to present
所以 轮播就是一个允许我们像幻灯片一样
a slideshow on the webpage, as you saw from the example.
展示一系列内容的有趣的组件
So the slides will keep sliding from left to right with a time duration,
这些幻灯片会每隔一段时间就向左滑
typically around three seconds between slides.
比较典型的是每隔三秒滑一下
The carousel also provides manual control so
轮播同样允许人为的控制
that the users can navigate to any of the slides within the carousel.
从而用户可以导航到其中任何一张幻灯片
We will look at all these in more detail next.
我们将会在后面更详细地叙述其实现
To add a carousel to your webpage, you will add a div with the classes carousel
为了加进一个轮播 我们使用的是 div
and slide and also the data attribute, data-ride, carousel.
然后对这个 div 设置 class="carousel slide" 和 data-ride="carousel"
This is what turns this into a carousel control by the JavaScript plugin.
通过 JavaScript 插件 这些代码将会把 这个 div 实现成一个轮播
To add slides to the carousel, we will,
为了将一张幻灯片插进轮播
inside the div that we have already introduced for the carousel,
我们会把这张幻灯片放在 div 下面
we will introduce another div with the class as carousel-inner.
记住每张幻灯片也是用 div 实现的
And inside this div,
然后对于幻灯片的这个 div
individual slides will be identified by an inner div class item.
你需要设置 class="item"
One of those inner divs will be identified as an active, meaning that when you
然后对其中一张幻灯片你需要额外地设置 class="active"
first go to the webpage, that particular slide will be presented to that user.
这意味着你的网页第一个展示的 是这个 div 下的内容
So that is the first slide in the slide deck being presented to the user.
可以把所有幻灯片看成一叠 然后 active 对应的 幻灯片就是这一叠最上面的一张
Now, each item can include an image together with a caption.
然后 每张幻灯片中可以加入一张图片 和对它的说明
So inside the item div,
加入图片的方法仍是直接用 img 标签
you would include another div with the class carousel caption.
加入说明的方法是应用一个设置了 class="carousel-caption" 的 div
So inside this inner div with carousel caption, you can include any HTML code.
在这个 div 中 你可以加入任何 HTML 代码
Typically, we would have a heading and some text included there.
比较典型的做法是加入一个标题和一些正文
Now, to introduce manual controls to the carousel,
接下来我们来引入对轮播的人为控制
we can have two different kinds of controls.
我们有许多种控制方法
One control allows you to select the specific slide.
其中一种是允许你选择特定的幻灯片
Now, this is introduced to the carousel in the form of darts at the bottom,
通常实现该控制的做法是在底部这里 加进几个圆点
as you can see in the image there.
如图所示
You can select any one of those slides by clicking one of the unfilled darts.
你可以通过点击其中任何一个未填充圆点
If you click on those unfilled darts, you will move to that particular slides there.
来导航到特定的幻灯片
The indicated controls are introduced into the carousel by including an ol
为了实现这个功能 我们需要用到 ol 标签
with the class carousel controls, and the list items in there will contain
对这个 ol 标签 我们需要设置 class="carousel-indicators"
two data attributes, the data target, which is the mycarousel,
然后还要设置数据属性 data-target="#mycarousel"
and then the data-slide-to, which will give the number of
和 data-slide-to="0"
the slide to which you should move when you click on that particular item.
其中的数字代表着想要导航到的幻灯片下标
Carousel's also introduced left and right indicators to the carousel.
我们还可以引入向左和向右的指示
So the left and right indicators can be shown as left and
如图所示 这两个指示
right arrow buttons on the two ends.
就是两个箭头
In this case, we are introducing them using the a tags with the classes
我们是用 a 标签来实现的 同时还要设置
left carousel-control and right carousel-control.
class="left carousel-control" 或 class="right carousel-control"
These classes can include inside a glyphicon, so in this case
然后为了让它长得像箭头 我们用了 glyphicon
I am using the left chevron and the right chevron as the glyphicon inside, so that
在这个栗子里 我用的是 chevron-left 和 chevron-right
these controls can be shown on the screen as the left and right buttons there.
从而能够实现右边这个图中的效果
Clicking on these will manually take you to the previous and
当你单击这两个箭头时 它们会把你带到
the next slide in the carousel slide deck.
上一张或下一张幻灯片
Now we will move on to the next exercise.
现在让我们来做下一个练习
There we will introduce a carousel into our webpage in the index storage TML page.
在这个练习里 我们将会亲自实现一个轮播
Now, we will also introduce manual controls to this carousel so
我们同时还会在这个轮播里实现 我们上面提到过的
we learn how to introduce manual controls and make use of them on our carousel.
对轮播的人为的控制 【翻译 - Carefree0910】